<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>TheCrafters001</title>
    <link href="https://thecrafters001.ga/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://thecrafters001.ga" />
    <updated>2020-05-01T16:25:22-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>TheCrafters001</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://thecrafters001.ga</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Get Your Team in Delta Green!</title>
        <author>
            <name>TheCrafters001</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://thecrafters001.ga/get-your-team-in-delta-green/"/>
        <id>https://thecrafters001.ga/get-your-team-in-delta-green/</id>

        <updated>2020-05-01T16:24:23-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://thecrafters001.ga/media/posts/19/deltagreen_banner2.png" alt="" />
                    Hi! I want you to come up with a team to be put into Delta Green! Your team has to be under these guidelines, however. You must not have your team over lvl 70. You can have all 6 pokemon NO LEGENDARIES OR MYTHICAL POKEMON.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://thecrafters001.ga/media/posts/19/deltagreen_banner2.png" alt="" />
                <figure class="post__image"></figure>
<p >Hi! I want you to come up with a team to be put into Delta Green!</p>
<p>Your team has to be under these guidelines, however.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>You must not have your team over lvl 70.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You can have all 6 pokemon</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>NO LEGENDARIES OR MYTHICAL POKEMON.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You can create a custom sprite using the one below.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You must state what trainer class you are (custom classes can be considered)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Because of limits in the editor, IVs can be edited, but EVs cannot.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>You must state what gender your Pokemon are (makes it easier on my life)</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>That is about it. No custom types are available in the game, and you are limited to pokemon from Gen 1 to Gen 5. This also means that Fairy type does not exist.</p>
<p>Happy Team Building!</p>
<figure class="post__image"><img src="https://thecrafters001.ga/media/posts/19/trchar005.png" alt="" width="128" height="192"></figure>
<p><img src="https://thecrafters001.ga/media/posts/19/trainer004.png" alt="" width="128" height="128"></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What I&#x27;m Doing about COVID-19</title>
        <author>
            <name>TheCrafters001</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://thecrafters001.ga/what-im-doing-about-covid-19/"/>
        <id>https://thecrafters001.ga/what-im-doing-about-covid-19/</id>

        <updated>2020-04-26T20:52:23-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>Hi, I know that COVID-19 is a touchy subject right now, but I have to cover it.</p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Hi, I know that COVID-19 is a touchy subject right now, but I have to cover it.</p>

<p>I know that everyone is worried about getting it, and there are a few points that I would like to make in this article.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e6sgt1cf0">How it affects my projects</h2>
<p>Well because I am at home almost always now, I have no choice but to work on my projects or watch videos on YouTube. So I have decided to take this time to resume proper development of <a href="https://thecrafters001.ga/pokemon-delta-green/">Pokémon Delta Green</a> and start a new project, <a href="https://forest-os.thecrafters001.ga/">Forest-OS</a>. But this is not the only thing I have to cover.</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e6sh49490">Pokémon Delta Green Updates</h3>
<p>Now that I have more time to work on Pokémon Delta Green, I have more time to make more quality updates, meaning that the time between updates has gone up. I believe that my projects should have quality over quantity, and I want to keep that stand point strong. A lot of other game companies spit out games too quick for consumers to handle, but I am slowly working on Delta Green. That is why the game has gone nearly 4 years in development, and has had 3 resets in that time. Expect more on Delta Green soon!</p>
<h3 id="mcetoc_1e6shhn9a1">What is Forest-OS?</h3>
<p>Forest-OS is an operating system built on VisualBasic on the .NET Framework! I plan to make this the first ever OS to interact with Windows in a big way! Forest-OS is not a shell replacement for Windows, it is an application. It helps the user by making the Windows experience better. This is an open source project using GNU GPL V3.0! You can check out the <a href="https://forest-os.thecrafters001.ga/">project page here</a>, and the <a href="https://github.com/TheCrafters001/Forest-OS">GitHub page here</a>.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e6shlkia0">When will I be happy with my website?</h2>
<p>I ask this to myself all the time, I keep updating my website to have new styles and I think the one that I have works the best for me.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e6shnoi01">What happened to Directs?</h2>
<p>There will be an update on <a href="https://direct.thecrafters001.ga/">the website</a> soon, look out for it!</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1e6shp0dh2">Conclusion</h2>
<p>I will not keep you reading for much longer, as everyone's time is currently nothing with all this going on in the world. I will be updating Delta Green as soon as I feel like it is ready to be updated. I know this is a hard time that we are all living in, but there is not much we can do right now, so please, stay safe!</p>
<p> - TheCrafters001</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Most Games and Software Have Been Added!</title>
        <author>
            <name>TheCrafters001</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://thecrafters001.ga/most-games-and-software-have-been-added/"/>
        <id>https://thecrafters001.ga/most-games-and-software-have-been-added/</id>

        <updated>2020-04-24T12:44:25-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I have added most of my Software and Games back to my site. I will not add all of them as most of them are either canceled or no-longer supported.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I have added most of my Software and Games back to my site. I will not add all of them as most of them are either canceled or no-longer supported.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How do I access old site stuff (ie: games, software, etc.)</title>
        <author>
            <name>TheCrafters001</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://thecrafters001.ga/how-do-i-access-old-site-stuff-ie-games-software-etc/"/>
        <id>https://thecrafters001.ga/how-do-i-access-old-site-stuff-ie-games-software-etc/</id>
            <category term="Help"/>

        <updated>2020-04-22T20:14:53-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Well, I am working on that. I plan to make hidden post that contain the links to other hidden post that have software/games/etc in them. But it will take some time. Once it is up am running, I will be sure to post about it!
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                Well, I am working on that. I plan to make hidden post that contain the links to other hidden post that have software/games/etc in them. But it will take some time. Once it is up am running, I will be sure to post about it!
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>New Website Design</title>
        <author>
            <name>TheCrafters001</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://thecrafters001.ga/new-website-design/"/>
        <id>https://thecrafters001.ga/new-website-design/</id>

        <updated>2020-04-21T21:49:54-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hi! I have redesigned the website!
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                Hi! I have redesigned the website!
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
